performancematters.com 2018-05-11

# Privacy Policy – Performance Matters

PERFORMANCE MATTERS PRIVACY POLICY

As much as we prioritize the success of students and educators, we care about protecting their privacy even more.

Protecting personally identifiable information is a company-wide priority. We’re committed to protecting your information, from student data to educator data to district data. As a sign of our commitment to protecting your privacy, we adhere to the [Student Privacy Pledge](https://studentprivacypledge.org/), which defines support standards for the safe and effective use of student information for students and teachers.  More than 1 million educators and 11 million students rely on our platform, and their privacy is of the utmost importance.

**Personal Information Protection Partnership**

Performance Matters (“Performance Matters” or “we”) partners with School Districts (“Districts”) to protect all student and teacher personally identifiable information (“PII” or “information”).  We recognize the importance of privacy to our website visitors and users of our online services (collectively, “you”).  The Performance Matters platforms enable Districts to regulate who is given an account to access student and teacher information.  Performance Matters does not sell or use PII for marketing purposes.  We use strong security protection on all information while it is transmitted and stored, and we employ security practices and monitoring to ensure the confidentiality and integrity of your information.

In order to provide you with the best possible experience it may be necessary for us to collect and store certain information about you.  This Privacy Policy explains what types of information we may collect and how we use that information to operate our public website (“Public Website”) and subscription online services (“Subscription Services”) and provide products and services to you.  We do not retain personal information longer than is required to provide the Subscribed Services.

We will not make material changes to this privacy policy without first providing notice to Districts, allowing them to make changes prior to using personal information in any manner inconsistent with the terms that they were initially provided.

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to our [_Terms of Use_](http://www.performancematters.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/01/Performance_Matters_Template_Subscription_Agreement.pdf).
